{
    "subject": "resource/Jane_Wall",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lagos",
    "human_readable": "Jane Wall was born in Lagos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.827675998210907,
            "question": "Where was Jane Wall born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398289442062378,
            "question": "Is Jane Wall still living in Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7269286513328552,
            "question": "When was Jane Wall born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5591522455215454,
            "question": "What nationality is Jane Wall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22875240445137024,
            "question": "Does Jane Wall have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20646175742149353,
            "question": "What does Jane Wall do for a living?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19370725750923157,
            "question": "Where did Jane Wall go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17213353514671326,
            "question": "Who are some famous people from Lagos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17071640491485596,
            "question": "What is Lagos known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08303716033697128,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Lagos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jane Wall was born in Lagos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8023_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Lagos known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8023_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous people from Lagos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8023_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Jane Wall go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8023_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8023_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8023/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) states that \"Jane Wall was born 1972 in Lagos, Nigeria.\" This directly supports the statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Jane Wall was born in Lagos, Nigeria. Therefore, the statement \"Jane Wall was born in Lagos\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}